Guide to the International Brotherhood of Teamsters Local 279, Decatur records, 1960-1978 IBT0081
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
IBT Local 279, Decatur records
1960-1978
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
International Brotherhood of Teamsters
International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen, and Helpers of America
IBT0081
0.75 Cubic Feet
The collection consists mainly of agreements and correspsondence with companies with whom IBT Local 279 bargained.
Scope and Contents
The collection consists of agreements and correspondence with comapies with whom IBT Local 279 bargained. There are subject files relating to the Davis -Bacon Act and union benefits.
Arrangement
The collection is arranged by company adn/or by subject.
Biographical / Historical
IBT Local 279 was originally charted on January 31, 1933. The charter was revised on December 1, 1940.
Conditions Governing Access
This collection is open for research.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
THis collection was transferred from the International Brotherhood of Teamsters.
Labor unions; Labor unions -- United States -- History -- 20th century; International Brotherhood of Teamsters; International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen, and Helpers of America
- LBT Local 279 Decatur, IL Arthur's Furniture, 1974-1976 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- LBT Local 279 Decatur, IL Scherer Freight Lines, Inc., 1969 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- LBT Local 279 Decatur, IL Illinois Farm Supply Co., 1970-1973 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- LBT Local 279 Decatur, IL Pepsi Cola Bottling Co., 1957-1975 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- LBT Local 279 Decatur, IL Tolley's Market, 1964-1970 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- LBT Local 279 Decatur, IL Van Pickerill and Sons, Co., 1977 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- LBT Local 279 Decatur, IL Clinton Welding Supply, Co., 1962 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- LBT Local 279 Decatur, IL Schluze and Burch Biscuit Co., 1960-1976 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- LBT Local 279 Decatur, IL Knox Motor Services, Inc., 1971-1977 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- LBT Local 279 Decatur, IL Archer-Daniels Midland Company, 1954-1960 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- LBT Local 279 Decatur, IL City Products Corporation, 1957-1969 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- LBT Local 279 Decatur, IL F.S. Services Inc., 1958-1975 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- LBT Local 279 Decatur, IL Skelley Oil Company, 1958-1976 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- LBT Local 279 Decatur, IL Armour and Company, 1970-1976 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- LBT Local 279 Decatur, IL Ashland Chemical Company, 1976-1978 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- LBT Local 279 Decatur, IL Heinkel Packing Co., 1957-1959 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- LBT Local 279 Decatur, IL FW Means and Company, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- LBT Local 279 Decatur, IL Board of Education District #61, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- LBT Local 279 Decatur, IL City Delivery Drivers and Dockmen Contract, 1953-1954 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- LBT Local 279 Decatur, IL Wilson and Company, Inc, 1957-1960 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- LBT Local 279 Decatur, IL Midwest Dairy Products, Inc, 1955-1957 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- LBT Local 279 Decatur, IL Perfect Potato Chips, Inc, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- LBT Local 279 Decatur, IL National By-Products, Inc, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- LBT Local 279 Decatur, IL Canteen, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- LBT Local 279 Decatur, IL Central, Southeast, and Southwest Pension Fund, 1971-1975 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- LBT Local 279 Decatur, IL W.G. Traver Supply Co. Pension Plan and Trust, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- LBT Local 279 Decatur, IL Welfare Fund Insurance Plans, 1957-1978 (Box 2, Folder 14)
- LBT Local 279 Decatur, IL Local 916, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 15)
- LBT Local 279 Decatur, IL Project Agreement for Maintenance, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 16)
- LBT Local 279 Decatur, IL Davis-Beacon Act, 1971-1973 (Box 2, Folder 17)
- LBT Local 279 Decatur, IL Bylaws and Supplemental Agreements, 1976-1979 (Box 2, Folder 18)